Finding Aid for Albert J. Schimpke collection of R.G. Peters materials, 1890-circa 1970
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Sound recordings
  - Digital Audio Files
    - Minnie Johnson Erickson Ramsey; Mrs. Emil Swanson; Anna Anderson, 1957 September 04, October 22; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 2], [88142-SR-36-2]; mp3 file; (Minnie Johnson Erickson Ramsey interviewed September 04, 1957, 2/3 front side; Mrs. Emil Swanson interviewed October 22, 1957, 1/3 front side; Anna Anderson; Interviewing Manistee residents about R.G. Peters and his contributions to the region.)
    - Walt Saurs, 1954 October 25; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [88142-SR-37-1]; mp3 file; (Walt Saurs discusses his interactions and experiences with R.G. Peters.)
      - [Part 2], [88142-SR-37-2]; mp3 file; (Walt Saurs discusses his interactions and experiences with R.G. Peters.)
    - Drayton Seaman, 1956 October 10; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [88142-SR-38-1]; mp3 file; (Interview with Drayton Seaman, resident of the Manistee area, discussing the logging industry and its effects on the region.)
      - [Part 2], [88142-SR-38-2]; mp3 file; (Interview with Drayton Seaman, resident of the Manistee area, discussing the logging industry and its effects on the region.)
    - Drayton Seaman; 1st half, 1957 February 05; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [88142-SR-39-1]; mp3 file; (Interview with Drayton Seaman, resident of the Manistee area, discussing the logging industry and its effects on the region.)
    - Curtis Shoup; Harry Darr, 1955 November 07, 1956 May 06; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [88142-SR-40-1]; mp3 file; (Curtis Shoup interviewed November 07, 1955, Harry Darr interviewed May 06, 1956. Interview with residents of the Manistee area in Michigan in the late 19th and early 20th century.)
      - [Part 2], [88142-SR-40-2]; mp3 file; (Curtis Shoup interviewed November 07, 1955, Harry Darr interviewed May 06, 1956. Interview with residents of the Manistee area in Michigan in the late 19th and early 20th century.)
    - Levi Sours, 1954 December 27; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [88142-SR-41-1]; mp3 file; (Interview with residents of the Manistee area in Michigan in the late 19th and early 20th century. Topics center around the lumber mill and railroading industry in the area.)
      - [Part 2], [88142-SR-41-2]; mp3 file; (Interview with residents of the Manistee area in Michigan in the late 19th and early 20th century. Topics center around the lumber mill and railroading industry in the area.)
    - Eric Sundberg, 1954 December 28; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [88142-SR-42-1]; mp3 file; (Reel 1; Interview about R.G. Peter's logging developments. Schimpke references a map of the region throughout the interview.)
      - [Part 2], [88142-SR-42-2]; mp3 file; (Reel 1; Interview about R.G. Peter's logging developments. Schimpke references a map of the region throughout the interview.)
    - Eric Sundberg, 1954 December 29; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [88142-SR-43-1]; mp3 file; (Reel 2; Interview about R.G. Peter's logging developments. Schimpke references a map of the region throughout the interview.)
      - [Part 2], [88142-SR-43-2]; mp3 file; (Reel 2; Interview about R.G. Peter's logging developments. Schimpke references a map of the region throughout the interview.)
    - Eric Sundberg, 1954 December 29; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [88142-SR-44-1]; mp3 file; (Reel 3; Interview about R.G. Peter's logging developments. Schimpke references a map of the region throughout the interview.)
    - Fred Syers, front half and half of back; John Battige, half of back, 1957 October 24; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [88142-SR-45-1]; mp3 file; (Fred Sayers discusses the logging industry and the construction of the railroads along the GR&I Line.)
      - [Part 2], [88142-SR-45-2]; mp3 file; (Fred Sayers discusses the logging industry and the construction of the railroads along the GR&I Line. John Battige discusses working on the railroad and his fellow workers.)
    - [Court case about R.G. Peters], C. F. Tallman; Emory Dumas, 1955 January 18, 19; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [88142-SR-46-1]; mp3 file; (Interview of C. F. Tallman on January 18, 1955; Emory Dumas interviewed on January 19, 1955. Schimpke reads a court case about R.G. Peters. The rest of the tape is oral history interviews with Manistee residents.)
      - [Part 2], [88142-SR-46-2]; mp3 file; (Interview of C. F. Tallman on January 18, 1955; Emory Dumas interviewed on January 19, 1955. Oral history interviews with Manistee residents about life in the area and the relationship of R.G. Peter's business ventures and the region.)
    - Mrs. Robert Vincent, 1954 December 30; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [88142-SR-47-1]; mp3 file; (Interview with Mrs. Robert Vincent regarding her first experience meeting R.G. Peters.)
      - [Part 2], [88142-SR-47-2]; mp3 file; (Interview with Mrs. Robert Vincent regarding her first experience meeting R.G. Peters.)
    - Clarence Warner; Robert Fox, 1955 January 06-07; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [88142-SR-48-1]; mp3 file; (Clarence Warner; Part I interviewed January 06, 1955; Robert Fox interviewed January 07, 1955; Oral history interviews with Manistee residents about life in the area and the relationship of R.G. Peter's business ventures and the region.)
      - [Part 2], [88142-SR-48-2]; mp3 file; (Clarence Warner; Part I interviewed January 06, 1955; Robert Fox interviewed January 07, 1955; Oral history interviews with Manistee residents about life in the area and the relationship of R.G. Peter's business ventures and the region.)
    - J. P. Weeks; H. S. Gray, 1955 October 20, 21; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [88142-SR-49-1]; mp3 file; (J. P. Weeks interviewed October 20, 1955; H. S. Gray interviewed October 21, 1955; Oral history interviews with Manistee residents about life in the area and the relationship of R.G. Peter's business ventures and the region.)
      - [Part 2], [88142-SR-49-2]; mp3 file; (J. P. Weeks interviewed October 20, 1955; H. S. Gray interviewed October 21, 1955; Oral history interviews with Manistee residents about life in the area and the relationship of R.G. Peter's business ventures and the region.)
  - Audio cassettes of interviews with associates of R.G. Peters, 1954-1960; 75 audiocassettes (Box 4)
    (listing of interviewees in box)
  - Reel-to-reel tape interviews, 29 tapes (Box 5)
    [staff use only; researchers should use cassettes in box 4]
  - Reel-to-reel tape interviews, 298 tapes (Box 6)
    (continued)